Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Well there's Carrie Lake, a gifted politician. I know I don't like the word politician but well she's just great. One of the best communicators I've ever seen in my life and it's fantastic that she is now the deputy CEO of the U.S. Agency for Global Media. Very interesting things happening there. But first have you heard about Maricopa County, Arizona elections? I've been deeply deeply suspicious and I know Carrie Lake as well.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Take a look at
Speaker 2: this, a tweet from Arizona State Senator Warren Peterson. "Last week I received and complied with a federal grand jury subpoena for records relating to the Arizona State Senate's 2020 audit of Maricopa County. The FBI has the records. Any other report is fake news.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): I sense that this is big and can go in all kinds of directions.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Carrie Lake, welcome back. I know you
Speaker 3: have some thoughts on all of this. How are you and what do you think? I
think a day
Speaker 4: of reckoning is coming in Maricopa County in Arizona, the really ground zero for
Speaker 5: the most corrupt elections in our country. And there's some stiff competition. I mean, I could name a few states, including Georgia and Michigan, Wisconsin, Pennsylvania and others. And this is why the president is pushing for the Save America Act. He really is about saving
America.
Speaker 5: America. I've been watching your program tonight,
Speaker 6: Greg, and all of the malcontents in the politics that you've talked about tonight, including Mamdami. You know, sometimes you scratch your head and say, how do these people get into office? Are people really that dumb? But what it really is, I believe, is elections are really that bad. And what we need to see is legal voters voting, not illegals,
Speaker 6: We need to see our voter rolls cleaned
Speaker 5: up and we need to show proof of citizenship to vote and have paper ballots, hand counted, no machines and no mail in ballots, except for if you're traveling or if you are in the military or if there's
Speaker 6: some sort of an emergency. It's really simple to clean up our elections and then we can know that the people we elect are really there because they won.
Speaker 6: Why do you think all these people in Congress and in the Senate don't want to pass the SAVE Act? I think a lot of them are very worried that if we really have truly
Speaker 7: honest elections, they won't be sitting in the Senate. They won't be sitting in the House of Representatives. Wow.
Speaker 8: How about that? Katie Hobbs,
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): the governor.
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): Can't stand it. Tweeted this. Arizonans are tired of election conspiracies and lies that undermine our democracy. Yeah. The FBI's reckless actions are an attack on Arizonans and undermine our rights as voters. They undermine our democracy.
Thou
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): protest too much a little bit. Just to be fair, what are your thoughts on that kind of denial? I'm
Speaker 10: really enjoying all of the folks out there who are
Speaker 5: very nervous, who have been gaslighting and trying to say that the elections are fine, nothing to see here. I'm really enjoying their tweets and their interviews right now because they seem to be
Speaker 5: trying to do major spin and what they don't realize is that the gaslighting they've inflicted
Speaker 6: upon us is not working anymore. Instead, we're just watching them spiral out of control and the truth is coming out. It's going to be coming out and it's going to flood out and eventually justice is coming. And I think they all know it.
Speaker 6: And they think it reminds me a lot of like O.J. Simpson when he just he carried that you know lie until the end that he wasn't involved and he didn't kill Nicole and everyone knew it the evidence was there and it was like he just wanted to keep saying it and everyone was just looking at him going dude we know what happened we know what happened in our elections the true
Speaker 11: conspiracy is the one they.
Speaker 11: are trying to spin that everything is fine but i feel so terrible for the people in my state of arizona the state's been captured a bunch of fraudsters have taken over and frankly we have a puppet government and we can't have that anymore we'll lose our country that's why the president is pushing for the save america act and i believe that eventually
Speaker 6: it will happen as more and more information comes out in the coming days eventually the dam will burst the water will flood in and there'll be no choice but
Speaker 11: to do something to protect
Speaker 11: and save our great nation through the most important thing we can do is fair and honest elections. When we have that,
Speaker 12: a lot of these other problems solve themselves. Well,
thank you,
Speaker 13: Carrie Lake. One day.
Speaker 13: i'm gonna have to talk to you about the oj simpson case i know
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): people say i'm crazy i there's a little there's more to that case than people realize just think about this who told us he was guilty the media and
the government
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): of los angeles
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): There's a lot to look at, and it infuriates people when I bring it up. And I was, he's a thousand percent guilty. I couldn't believe it when he was acquitted. There's a story there, which I've told before, and people get so mad.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): But I'm going to revisit
Speaker 3: it at some point here and with you. I hope you'll be open-minded. I know you will be.
Speaker 15: Give me a call. Call
me. You've got my number. I haven't
Speaker 16: heard this one. I'm curious. You've got my number. But we want to pass the Save America Act. Pressure your senators. Call them. Write them. Be kind. Be peaceful. But call them and write them and remind them that you're the boss. You are the voter.
Speaker 18: That's who they represent. So much more important than O.J.,
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): quite frankly. And I know you're going to work that thing out with the employees. That's your authority, not some judges. All the
Speaker 19: best. Apparently a D.C. district court judge runs the agency. Ain't
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): going to stand. Thank you very much. We'll be right back.